list-alert.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Policy_**   

**Effective Date - September 15, 2009**   

We recognize the importance of your privacy. Please read the following policy (the "Privacy Policy") to understand how your information will be treated. These privacy practices apply to the websites, associated widgets, mobile applications and other distribution platforms (the "Sites") operated by JoMa Ventures, Inc. ("JoMa").   

Our Sites and associated communications from us may contain links to third-party sites, which are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you read the privacy policy of any such sites that you visit. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Sites.   

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (which may include email notification of policy changes for those that have created accounts and provided an email address). Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date. Therefore, we encourage you to check the date of our Privacy Policy whenever you visit the Sites for any updates or changes.   

**Consent**

By visiting our Sites, you are consenting to the information collection, use and sharing practices described in this Privacy Policy, as modified from time to time by us. In order to access certain functionalities of the Sites you will be required to register by providing certain information   

**What this Privacy Policy Does NOT Address**

This Privacy Policy does not address the data management practices and policies of and information usage policies of other sites to which the Sites may link to or on which a JoMa widget may be installed.   

**Information We Collect**

The information we collect from visitors to our Sites depends upon how visitors choose to interact with us through the Sites. We offer some services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us. For example, you can read materials such as our blogs without providing personal information. However, using our full range of services involves providing personal information to us. Personal information is information that can be used to identify you, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number or billing information. When you register with us and sign in to our Sites, we recognize that you are not anonymous to us.   

The following is a list of types of information we may collect and ways in which it is collected:   

_Information you provide._ When you sign up for a service that require registration, we ask you for personal information such as your name and email address. We also collect information you provide when requesting a service, and this information may, among other things, include personal information or reveal details about your preferences. We typically store and maintain the information collected.   

_Logged information._ We automatically collect and store some information that you do not actively provide, such as your internet protocol (IP) address, software and hardware attributes such as browser type, the date and time of your visit, and the last website you visited prior to visiting the Sites. This information is used to enhance the services we provide to you.   

_Cookies._ When you visit the Sites, we send one or more cookies (that is, small text files) to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can change your browser's settings to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features and services will not function properly if cookies are disabled. Cookies may contain account information such as your user name and password if you opt in to the automatic login option.   

_Other Internet technology._ We may use other technology, such as pixel tags and web beacons, to track use of our Sites. We may also include web beacons in email messages, newsletters, or other communications to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. We may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our Sites from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors, to deliver targeted advertisements, and to measure the usage and effectiveness of our Sites and our online advertising and other content and activities.   

**How We Use The Information**

In general we use personal and other information collected through the Sites to fulfill your requests for services, contact you, customize advertising and content, and improve our services. More specifically, we use personal and other information as follows:   

_Provide Services._ To provide our services, for example to deliver a message to the addresses or other destinations you have specified.    

_Communicate._ Use your personal information to communicate with you generally, for example to respond to a query from you, or to provide you with updates or information concerning our services or the services of other companies that we believe you may be interested in. For information regarding opting out of some of these communications, please see "Your Choices" below.   

_Customization._ To customize the advertising and content that you see on the Sites and in associated communications. For example, the Sites and associated communications from us may include targeted advertisements based on personal and other information. We do not provide any information to the advertiser or ad serving company that would personally identify you when you view or interact with a targeted ad, but advertisers and ad serving companies may assume that people who interact with or view targeted ads meet the targeting criteria.    

_Research._ To improve our services we conduct research on how are services are used. For example, we may request that you complete user surveys, and use the resulting data to improve the Sites.   

_Improve Usability._ We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people use the Sites. We also use other Internet technology, as described above under "Information We Collect."   

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We do not sell, share or disclose your contact information or personal information except to provide the services you request, when you give us permission, and in the following cases:   

_Providing Services._ Personal and other information is anonymously shared with our selected suppliers, service providers and partner sites in connection with providing services to you. For example, we may provide such information to third parties in connection with operating and maintaining the Sites, fulfilling your requests for services, processing credit card payments (if applicable), performing business and sales analysis, and offering contests or conducting surveys. We do not provide contact details to other companies for their marketing or mailing list unless you personally opt-in to other companies services.   

_Ad Targeting._ Non-personally identifiable information is provided to third-party advertisers, and ad serving companies as described in the preceding section of this Privacy Policy ("How We Use The Information"). If you choose to interact with an advertisement on the Sites or in an associated communication from us, for example by clicking on an ad you will leave the Sites and your interactions with that third party will not be governed by this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use. We do not control how any third party may collect, use, or disclose your personal or other information.    

_Content Sharing._ Content (meaning any materials, including, without limitation, text, pictures, graphics, sound files and other files and the selection and arrangement thereof, the "Content") that you make available publicly on the Sites is generally displayed to other visitors to the Sites. Content that you make available publicly may be collected and used by others, and we cannot control what other users do with this Content.    

_Complying With The Law._ We disclose personal and other information if we have a good-faith belief that the disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, legal process or an enforceable government request; to enforce applicable terms of use for our services; to detect, prevent or otherwise address illegal activity, fraud, or security issues; or to protect the property or safety of our users, JoMa, or the public as required or permitted by law.   

_Change of Control._ In connection with a significant transaction involving JoMa, such as a merger or acquisition, we may transfer personal and other information to another party, but we will provide a notice before your personal information becomes subject to the privacy policy of another company.

_Aggregate Data._ We may share aggregated information with third parties, such as usage statistics or demographic trends regarding our users. This data does not include personal information.   

**Your Choices**

As a user of the Sites you have the following options:    

_Account Review._ If you have an account with us, you can review and update your account information (such as your name and contact information) online by making the appropriate selections or changes. We make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and the ability to correct the information if it is inaccurate or to delete it at your request (if it is not required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes). We require users to reliably identify themselves and the information they wish to access, correct, or remove before processing these requests, and we may decline to process requests that we believe in good faith are unreasonable or unduly burdensome (such as requests that are repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be impractical to satisfy).   

_Service Review._ You can add, edit, pause or remove services that you have subscribed to by logging into the Sites.    

_Deactivate Account._ You can deactivate your account with us at any time by making the appropriate selections. If you deactivate your account and later wish to reopen it and again receive services from us, you may be required to re-enter your account information and re-subscribe to any services you wish to receive. However, if you deactivate your account we may retain certain information associated with your account for recordkeeping. Further, we generally do not remove information that you have made publicly available, and information that has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy may be retained by those third parties and will be subject to their policies, and not this Privacy Policy.   

_Opt Out._ If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We do reserve the right to contact you on matters that we believe in good faith to be urgent or of particular importance even if you opt out from other communications, but these would not include marketing communications.   

**Information Security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of personal information. These measures include administrative and physical security measures intended to guard against unauthorized access to personal data. No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is one hundred percent secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.   

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email or at the following mailing address:   

JoMa Ventures, Inc.

12405 Venice Boulevard, Suite 133

Los Angeles

California, 90066

USA
